aboutads.info 2018-12-23

# Privacy Policy | www.aboutads.info

This Privacy Policy explains how the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) collects and uses the information you provide to us, to help you make informed decisions when you use our various websites (“Sites”) and AppChoices mobile application (“App”), collectively our Digital Properties. Please be sure to read this entire Privacy Policy before using our Digital Properties. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, then you should not use our Digital Properties. This Privacy Policy is specifically incorporated into the Terms of Service, which governs your use of our Digital Properties.

When you visit or use our Digital Properties, we may collect the following types of information:

  * Personal information you choose to provide to us such as your name, mailing address, and email address. You may provide this information, for example, when you make requests for information or assistance.
  * Technical information including, but not limited to, browser type, IP address, mobile device type and identifier, screen resolution, operating system, the date and time of a visit or use, the pages visited on this Site and areas accessed in the App, the time spent viewing the Digital Properties, and return visits to the Digital Properties.
  * Aggregated information as you and others browse and use our Digital Properties.

We may use the information we collect from you for purposes such as:

  * To respond to your inquires and requests;
  * To operate our Digital Properties and improve your experience;
  * To identify or remediate possible threats to the Site’s security;
  * To conduct research about your use of the Digital Properties and our services;
  * To effectuate your opt-out choices; and
  * For any other purpose specified at time of collection.

We use Google Analytics to better understand how visitors interact with our Sites. This service provides technical data including but not limited to data on where visitors came from, what actions they took on our Sites, and where visitors went when they left our Sites. We use this information to improve your experience when visiting our Sites. Please click [here](http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html) to learn more about this service and how to opt out of data collection by Google Analytics. We may also work with other partners to conduct research surveys in order to improve the user experience on our Digital Properties. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these partners to learn about their data practices.  We may also work with partners to help operate our Digital Properties and features offered therein.  These partners may use cookies or similar technologies for these purposes.

Through some of our Digital Properties, you are able to exercise choice with respect to certain data practices of companies participating in the choice tools we provide. When you exercise your choice, we may share some information collected from you, your computer, or your mobile device with these companies so that they may honor your requests concerning their data collection practices. Additionally, we may share information with service providers who may assist us in responding to your inquiries or requests, or otherwise perform some business or operational function for us. We may also disclose personal information about you if required to do so by law, including without limitation, by search warrant, subpoena or court order; to protect our and third party rights; and for purposes disclosed at time of collection.

We take reasonable measures to help maintain data we collect through our Digital Properties in a secure manner.

###  Links to third party sites

Our Digital Properties may contain links to other websites operated by third parties we do not control and this Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected through our Digital Properties. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these other websites.

From time to time, we may update this Privacy Policy. We will notify you of any material changes to our Privacy Policy by posting any updated policies on this page. We encourage you to visit this area frequently to stay informed.

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@aboutads.info](mailto:privacy@aboutads.info).

Last Updated: May 18, 2017
